

Profile

Short story

I'm a low profile person who loves to just get things done.

Born in Lisbon, Portugal, moved right away to a place near the beautiful Serra da Estrela - then to Ribatejo where I spent most of my childhood.

Now I'm back in Lisbon again working remotely supporting different teams in different geographies.

I'm currently working at Critical Techworks creating visual experiences for the BMW Group's driving machines and mobility services of the future.

I admire simple but elegant visual designs, have a deep interest in design systems, and I'm also a front-end enthusiast.

Interests

Life







Work





N Design Systems

Experience

2010 _ Present

Product Designer

Critical TechWorks | BMW Group

2014-2019

UI & UX Designer

Instituto Superior Técnico, University of Lisbon

2010-2014

Digital Content Manager

Cienciapt.net

201

Intern Designer

City Hall of Cartaxo

Education

2012-2015

Master in New Media and Web Practices

NOVA School of Social Sciences and Humanities

2008-2011

Bachelor in Multimedia Communication and Education

Polytechnic Institute of Santarém

Skills

Design





Adobe CC

Front-end

THIML

GCSS

JS JS

Git